const data = [
    {
      question: "EL as a covenant name of God means?",
      incorrectAnswers: [
        "Lord",
        "Great One",
        "Father",
      ],
      correctAnswer: "God, Mighty One",
    },
  
    {
      question: "EL ELYON means?",
      incorrectAnswers: [
        "Great God",
        "Constant One",
        "Mighty One",
      ],
      correctAnswer: "The Most High",
    },
    {
      question: "Which Scripture describes God as EL ELYON?",
      incorrectAnswers: ["Deuteronomy 30:19", "Genesis 30:8", "Leviticus 2:3"],
      correctAnswer: "Deuteronomy 32:8",
    },
    {
      question: "EL OLAM means?",
      incorrectAnswers: ["The Great God", "The Powerful God", "The I am"],
      correctAnswer: "The Everlasting God",
    },
    {
      question: "[Trust ye in the Lord for ever: for in the Lord JEHOVAH is everlasting strength] is found where?",
      incorrectAnswers: [
        "Proverbs 3:5",
        "Isaiah 49:11",
        "Proverbs 3:4",
      ],
      correctAnswer: "Isaiah 26:4",
    },
    {
      question: "EL SHADDAI means?",
      incorrectAnswers: [
        "Great God",
        "Sovereign King",
        "The Faithful God",
      ],
      correctAnswer: "The Almighty God",
    },
    {
      question: "[And when Abram was ninety years old and nine, the Lord appeared to Abram, and said unto him, I am the Almighty God; walk before me, and be thou perfect] can be found where?",
      incorrectAnswers: ["Psalm 150:2", "Genesis 49:10", "Psalm 109:2"],
      correctAnswer: "Genesis 17:1",
    },
    {
      question: "ADONAI means?",
      incorrectAnswers: [
        "Eternal, Strong, King",
        "Good, Holy, Just",
        "Great, Mighty, God",
      ],
      correctAnswer: "Lord, Master, Owner, Ruler",
    },
    {
        question: "JEHOVAH: the personal NAME of God in His relationship as __________.?",
        incorrectAnswers: [
          "SAVIOUR",
          "RULER",
          "KING",
        ],
        correctAnswer: "REDEEMER",
    },
    {
        question: "JEHOVAH ELOHIM means?",
        incorrectAnswers: [
          "Great God",
          "Powerful God",
          "Sufficient God",
        ],
        correctAnswer: "Supreme God",
    },
    {
      question: "[These are the generations of the heavens and of the earth when they were created, in the day that the Lord God [Jehovah Elohim] made the earth and the heavens] is found where?",
      incorrectAnswers: [
        "Genesis 3:2",
        "Genesis 20:2",
        "Genesis 4:2",
      ],
      correctAnswer: "Genesis 2:4",
  },
  {
    question: "JEHOVAH JIREH means? ",
    incorrectAnswers: [
      "The Lord has it all",
      "The Lord will Supply",
      "The Lord will Give",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "The Lord will Provide",
  },
  {
    question: "[So Abraham called the name of that place The Lord Will Provide [Jehovah Jireh]. And it is said to this day, On the mount of the Lord it will be provided] is found where?",
    incorrectAnswers: [
      "Genesis 5:8",
      "Genesis 10:4",
      "Genesis 22:4",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Genesis 22:14",
  },
  {
    question: "[He who did not withhold or spare [even] His own Son but gave Him up for us all, will He not also with Him freely and graciously give us all [other] things?] is found where?",
    incorrectAnswers: [
      "John 5:8",
      "John 8:32",
      "Romans 5:8",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Romans 8:32",
  },
  {
    question: "JEHOVAH RAPHA means?",
    incorrectAnswers: [
      "The Lord my Saviour",
      "The Lord my Doctor",
      "The Lord my Strength",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "The Lord my Healer",
  },
  {
    question: "JEHOVAH NISSI means?",
    incorrectAnswers: [
      "The Lord my Saviour",
      "The Lord my Peace",
      "The Lord my protector",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "The Lord my Banner",
  },
  {
    question: "[He brought me to the banqueting house, and His banner over me was love] is found where?",
    incorrectAnswers: [
      "Psalm 2:4",
      "Proverbs 4:2",
      "Song of Solomon 4:2",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Song of Solomon 2:4",
  },
  {
    question: "JEHOVAH SHALOM means?",
    incorrectAnswers: [
      "The Lord, He is God",
      "The Lord my Comforter",
      "The Lord my Saviour",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "The Lord my Peace",
  },
  {
    question: "[Peace I leave with you, my peace I give unto you: not as the world giveth, give I unto you. Let not your heart be troubled, neither let it be afraid] is found where?",
    incorrectAnswers: [
      "Mark 12:2",
      "John 2:14",
      "John 27:14",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "John 14:27",
  },
  {
    question: "JEHOVAH RAAH (ROI or ROHI) means?",
    incorrectAnswers: [
      "The Lord my Saviour",
      "The Lord my Keeper",
      "The Lord my Peace",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "The Lord my Shepherd",
  },
  {
    question: "[I am the Good Shepherd. The Good Shepherd risks and lays down His [own] life for the sheep] is found where?",
    incorrectAnswers: [
      "John 10:2",
      "Luke 10:19",
      "John 10:20",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "John 10:11",
  },
  {
    question: "[And when the Chief Shepherd appears, you will receive the crown of glory that does not fade away] is found where?",
    incorrectAnswers: [
      "Romans 5:10",
      "John 10:2",
      "1 Peter 5:3",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "1 Peter 5:4",
  },
  {
    question: "JEHOVAH TSIDKENU means?",
    incorrectAnswers: [
      "The Lord our Sanctifier",
      "The Lord our Purity",
      "The Lord our Holiness",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "The Lord our Righteousness",
  },
  {
    question: "[In His days Judah shall be saved and Israel shall dwell safely: and this is His name by which He shall be called: The Lord Our Righteousness] is found where?",
    incorrectAnswers: [
      "Job 2:3",
      "John 3:17",
      "Jeremiah 29:11",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Jeremiah 23:6",
  },
  {
    question: "JEHOVAH SABAOTH/TSEBAOTH means?",
    incorrectAnswers: [
      "The Lord our Banner",
      "The Supreme God",
      "The Lord of Heaven",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "The Lord of Hosts",
  },
  {
    question: "JEHOVAH SHAMMAH means?",
    incorrectAnswers: [
      "The Lord is King",
      "The Lord is Able",
      "The Lord is Here",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "The Lord is there",
  },
  {
    question: "[5) For He Himself has said, 'I will never leave you nor forsake you.'  6) So we may boldly say: 'The Lord is my helper; I will not fear. What can man do to me?'] is found where?",
    incorrectAnswers: [
      "John 13:5",
      "Hebrews 13:6",
      "Hebrews 13:5",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Hebrews 13:5b-6",
  },
  {
    question: "[Elisha's servant's eyes are opened to see the hosts of God â€“ horses and chariots of fire - surrounding the city] can be found where?",
    incorrectAnswers: [
      "1 Peter 2:9-10",
      "Psalm 13:2-9",
      "2 Kings 7:13-17",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "2 Kings 6:13-17",
  },
  {
    question: "[Who is [He then] this King of glory? The Lord of hosts, He is the King of glory] is found where?",
    incorrectAnswers: [
      "Ephesians 2:1",
      "James 2:4",
      "Proverbs 10:2",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Psalm 24:10",
  },
  {
    question: "[But of Him are ye in Christ Jesus, who of God is made unto us wisdom, and righteousness, and sanctification, and redemption] can be found where?",
    incorrectAnswers: [
      "Romans 2:8",
      "John 1:12",
      "1 Corinthians 1:20",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "1 Corinthians 1:30",
  },
  ];
  
  export default data;